Mss.B.W564
American Philosophical Society
- I. Princeton University Correspondence and Files, 1913-1976 (Volume 1-5, Box 1-33)
  - Misner, Charles W., 1955-1974, n.d.; 2.0 folders (Box 18)
    Bardeen, James; Bargmann, [V.] (1955); Bergmann, [Peter G.] (1956); Caianiello, [Eduardo] (1955); Conner, [?] (1955); Everett, [Hugh III] (1955); Feynman, Rishard P. (1955); W. H. Freeman and Co., Publishers (1972); Geroch, Robert Paul; Hartle, James B.; Khuri, [?] (1955); Komar, [Arthur]; Phillips, [?] (1955); Putnam, [Peter]; Spencer, D.C. (1955-1956); Thorne, Kip S. (1972); Wightman, [Arthur Strong] (1955); Wigner, [Eugene P.]. -- See also Series I: Eisenhart, Luther P. (1957); W. H. Freeman and Co., Publishers; Matzner, Richard A.; Ozsvath, Istvan; Scott, Dana; Thorne, Kip S.; Weber, Joseph
    - Folder #1, 1955-1969 (Box 18)
    - Folder #2, 1970-1974, n.d. (Box 18)
  - Mitskievic, N. V., 1969, n.d. (Box 18)
  - Mittelstaedt, P., 1966 (Box 18)
    In German
  - Miyakawa, Kozaburo, 1960 (Box 18)
  - Mjolsness, Ray, 1958 (Box 18)
  - Moe, Henry Allen, 1971-1975 (Box 18)
  - Moffat, John, 1957 (Box 18)
    -- See also Series I: Einstein, Albert (1953)
  - Moffitt, John, 1975-1976 (Box 18)
  - Mollenauer, James, 1964 (Box 18)
    Halpern, Isaac
  - Moller, Christian, 1958-1974 (Box 18)
    -- See also Series I: Belinfante, Fred J.
  - Moncrief, Vincent, 1972-1976 (Box 18)
    -- See also Series I: Teitelboim, Claudio
  - Montel, Harold, [1975] (Box 18)
  - Montesinos Amilibia, Angel, 1973-1974 (Box 18)
  - Montgomery, D. J., 1955 (Box 18)
  - Montroll, Elliott Waters, 1965, n.d. (Box 18)
    -- See also Series I: Destouches, J. L.
  - Moore, Henry, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Moore, Ruth, 1964-1966 (Box 18)
    Von Neumann, [John]
  - Moravsik, Michael J., 1965 (Box 18)
  - Morgenstern, Oskar, 1957-1975 (Box 18)
    Teller, Edward. -- See also Series I: Hutchisson, Elmer; Killian, James R.
  - Moroz, Boris Z., 1975-1976 (Box 18)
  - Morrison, Philip, 1969-1974 (Box 18)
  - Moshinsky, Marcos, 1969-1974 (Box 18)
  - Moshir, Moshen Mehrdad, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Mossbauer, Rudolf L., 1967 (Box 18)
    -- See also Series I: Dessauer, Gerhard
  - Motyl, Elzbieta, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Motz, Lloyd, 1973 (Box 18)
    Sarfatt[i], Jack
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1973 (Box 18, Box OS1)
    Truman, David B. -- See also Oversize for poster for lecture to be given at Mount Holyoke entitled, "The Black Hole and the End of Time."
  - Mowat, John G., 1974 (Box 18)
    Carr, Howard E.
  - Moyer, Burton Jones, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Muetterties, Earl L., 1968 (Box 18)
  - Mugur-Schachter, M[ioara], 1974 (Box 18)
  - Muiv, O., 1972 (Box 18)
  - Mukunda, Narasimhaiengar, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Muller-Markus, Siegfried, 1969-1974 (Box 18)
  - Mulliken, Robert S., 1966 (Box 18)
  - Munch, Guido, 1967 (Box 18)
  - Murnaghan, Francis, 1968-1974 (Box 18)
  - Murphy, Charles, 1957 (Box 18)
  - Myers, Allen C., 1963 (Box 18)
  - Nagle, Darragh E., 1969 (Box 19)
  - Nambu, Y., n.d. (Box 19)
  - Narlikar, Jayant V., 1967-1976 (Box 19)
  - Nash, Edward Thomas, 1964-1965, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Nassivera, John C., 1972 (Box 19)
  - Nathan, Otto, 1971-1975 (Box 19)
    -- See also Series I: Einstein Papers
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1951-1976 (Box 19)
    Bronk, Detlev W.; Dryden, Hugh L.; Fowler, William A.; Taylor, Calvin W.; Zacharias, J.R. -- See also Series Institute for Defense Analyses; Pedersen, Flemming
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1971 (Box 19)
  - National Educational Television and Radio Center, 1962 (Box 19)
  - National Science Foundation, 1953-1974, n.d. (Box 19)
  - NATO. American Advisory Group on NATO Scientific and Technical Personnel, 1955-1958; 5.0 folders (Box 19)
    Advisory Committee to the Office of Scientific Personnel (1956); Amaldi, E[duardo] (1957); Bakker, C.J. (1957); Bronk, Detlev W. (1957); Brossel, J. (1957); Caianiello, [Eduardo] (1957); CERN (1957); Courant, R. (1957) DeWitt-Morette, [Cecile] (1957); Drysdale, Taylor (1958); Emerling, Lowell (1957); Ford Foundation (1957); Fort, Richard (1957); Fosdick, Dorothy ("Dickie") (1957); Gorter, C.J. (1957); Griggs, David T. (1957-58); Haskins, Caryl P. (1957); Jackson, Henry M. (1957-58); Johnston, Eric (1957); Kastler, A. (1957); Kelly, Harry C. (1957); Killian, J[ames] R., Jr. (1957); Langham, Wright H. (1955); Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory (1955); Major, Robert (1957); Mansfield, Kenneth (1957); Mayer, Maria Goeppert (1957); Mettler, R.F. (1957); Meyerhoff, Howard A. (1957); Mott, N.F. (1957); NATO. Committee on Scientific and Technical Personnel ([1957]); Nielsen, Jakob (1957); Otting, William J. (1957); Pines, David (1957); Polvani, G. (1957); Ramsey, Norman F. (1958); Robertson, H.P. (1957); Rockefeller Foundation (1957); Sarnoff, David (1957); Spaak, P.H. (1957); Teller, Edward (1957); Trytten, M.H. ([1957]); von Karman, Theodore (1957); Weaver, Warren (1957); Wright, William E. (1957)
  - Nature, 1970 (Box 19)
    Maddox, John
  - Nauenberg, Michael, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Naumann, Robert A., 1960-1968 (Box 19)
  - Ne'eman, Yuval, 1973 (Box 19)
    -- See also Series I: Sakharov, Andrei
  - Nell, Edward J., 1972 (Box 19)
  - Nelson, Alfred T., 1974 (Box 19)
  - Nelson's Encyclopedia, 1945-1946 (Box 19)
  - Nester, Jim, 1976 (Box 19)
  - New England Institute, 1966 (Box 19)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1962-1976 (Box 19)
  - Newman, Charles Michael, 1967 (Box 19)
  - Nickerson, J. Charles, 1973 (Box 20)
  - Niels Bohr Institute, 1966-1967 (Box 20)
    Bohr, Aage; Ford Foundation
  - Nielsen, Harald Herborg, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Nier, Alfred O. C., 1955 (Box 20)
    -- See also Series I: Weber, Joseph (1958)
  - Nikhilananda, Swami, 1957 (Box 20)
  - Nilsson, Sven Gosta, [1954] (Box 20)
  - Nirenberg, Louis, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Nirenberg, Marshall Warren, 1967 (Box 20)
  - Noble, Julian Victor, 1963-1965 (Box 20)
  - Nordtvedk, Kenneth, Jr., 1971 (Box 20)
  - Novello, M., 1976 (Box 20)
  - Novikov, I[gor] D., 1967-1974 (Box 20)
    Thorne, Kip S.
  - Noyes, H. Pierre, 1970-1973, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Nussenzveig, H. M[oyses], 1970, n.d. (Box 20)
    Hamburger, Ernesto
  - Nutku, Yavuz, 1969-1976 (Box 20)
  - Oberlin College, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Obregon, Octavio, 1976 (Box 20)
  - O'Driscoll, Sean, 1974-1975 (Box 20)
  - Ogden, Peter Michael, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Ohanian, Hans Christoph, 1965-1976 (Box 20)
    -- See also Series I: Ford, Lawrence Howard (1976)
  - Okerson, David J., 1968-1973 (Box 20)
    Peierls, Rudolf E.
  - Okoye, Sam E., 1972 (Box 20)
  - Oldham, Geoffrey, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Oliveira, Colber G. de, 1961 (Box 20)
    Tiomno, Jayme
  - O'Murchadha, Niall Seamus, 1971-1976 (Box 20)
  - O'Neill, Gerard K., 1966-1974 (Box 20)
  - Onsager, L., n.d. (Box 20)
  - Oorh, Bram, 1961 (Box 20)
  - Oort, Jan H., 1958-1974 (Box 20)
  - Opher, Reuven, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1954-1967 (Box 20)
    Bethe, Hans A.; Livingston, M. Stanley; Strauss, Lewis; Weisskopf, Victor F. -- See also Series I: Hutchisson, Elmer; Putnam, Mildred A.
  - Ornstein, Robert E., 1973-1976 (Box 20)
    Stramberger, Pauline
  - Osterreichische Nationalbibliothek, 1972-1974 (Box 20)
    Wieser, Walter G.
  - Ostriker, Jeremiah, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Overbeck, William P., 1969 (Box 20)
  - Ovrut, Burt, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Ozsvath, Istvan, 1963 (Box 20)
  - Pachner, Jaroslav, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Pagels, Heinz Rudolf, 1959-1974 (Box 20)
  - Pais, Abraham, 1947-1961 (Box 20)
    Bohr, Niels (1947)
  - Pake, George Edward, 1963-1965, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Palmatier, [?], 1959 (Box 20)
  - Palmer, A. Jay, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Pandres, Dave, Jr., 1968, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Papapetrou, A., 1964-1969 (Box 20)
    Case, Kenneth Myron
  - Pardee, Arthur Beck, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Pariseau, [?], n.d. (Box 20)
  - Parker, Leonard, 1971-1974, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Parsegian, V. L., 1962 (Box 20)
  - Partridge, R. Bruce, [1967]-1972 (Box 20)
  - Patel, J. C., 1974 (Box 20)
    Rege, D. V.
  - Patton, Charles M., 1971-1976, n.d. (Box 20)
    Wohl, David Harris
  - Pauli, Hertha, 1973 (Box 20)
  - Pauli, W[olfgang], 1972 (Box 20)
    Jordan, [Pascual]
  - Pavelle, Richard, 1969-1973 (Box 20)
  - Peat, F. David, n.d. (Box 20)
    -- See also Series I: Penrose, Roger; Post, E. J.
  - Pedersen, Flemming B., 1969 (Box 20)
    National Academy of Sciences
  - Peebles, Philip James Edwin, 1962-1974 (Box 20)
    Gunn, J. -- See also Series I: Dicke, Robert H. (1965)
  - Peierls, Rudolf E. (Sir), 1957-1974 (Box 20)
    -- See also Series I: Okerson, David J
  - Pekeris, Chaim Lieb, 1974-1976 (Box 20)
  - Pendergast, Richard J., 1964 (Box 20)
  - Penrose, Roger, 1959-1973 (Box 20)
    Hawking, Stephen; Peat, F. David. -- See also Series I: Hawking, Stephen; Scott, Dana S.
  - Pereira, Carlos Martin, 1967-1975 (Box 20)
    Kuchar, Karel V. (1972); York, James W., Jr. (1972)
  - Peres, Asher, 1962-1972 (Box 20)
    Rosen, Nathan. -- See also Series I: Rosen, Nathan
  - Pergamon Press, 1958 (Box 20)
  - Perk, Susanne (Mrs. George D.), 1952 (Box 20)
  - Perkins, G. A., 1955 (Box 20)
  - Perlman, I., 1950 (Box 20)
  - Peters, Philip C., 1974-1975 (Box 20)
  - Petersen, Aage, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
    -- See also Series I: Everett, Hugh III; Hempel, C. G. (Peter)
  - Petterson, Jacobus A., 1976 (Box 20)
  - Petti, Richard, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - Pham, Mau Quan, 1967 (Box 20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Philips, Thomas O., 1959-1966 (Box 20)
  - Phipps, T. E., Jr., 1974 (Box 20)
  - Physical Review, 1966-1975 (Box 20)
    Goudsmit, Samuel A. -- See also Series I: Kittel, Charles; Toll, John S. (1956); Weber, Joseph (1969). -- See also Series III: Causality and Dispersion Theory
  - Physics Today, 1967-1976 (Box 20)
    Davis, Harold L.; Ellis, Hobart; Harvey, Alexander; Jammer, Max (1975); Taylor, Edwin F. -- See also Series I: DeWitt-Morette, Cecile
  - Pierce, John, 1962-1971 (Box 21)
  - Pines, David, 1954-1973 (Box 21)
    -- See also Series I: Reviews of Modern Physics
  - Pinkas, Paul P., Jr., 1974 (Box 21)
  - Pinkus, David, [1956] (Box 21)
  - Piragas, [?], 1972 (Box 21)
  - Pirani, Felix A. E., 1959-1972 (Box 21)
    Cantoni, Vittorio
  - Piron, C., 1973 (Box 21)
    Jauch, Josef Maria
  - Piroue, Pierre A., n.d. (Box 21)
  - Plass, Gilbert N., 1954-1976 (Box 21)
  - Platt, John Rader, 1966 (Box 21)
  - Plebanski, Jerzy [F.], 1959-1975 (Box 21)
  - Pleijel, Ake, 1953-1954 (Box 21)
  - Polak, Joel, 1966 (Box 21)
  - Pollock, Robert E., 1966, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Pommaret, J. F., 1973-1974 (Box 21)
    Teitelboim, Claudio
  - Post, E[vert] J., 1966-1974 (Box 21)
    Peat, F. David
  - Post, Richard Freeman, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Poultney, Sherman King, 1959-1965 (Box 21)
  - Poveda, Arcadio, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Power, Edwin A., 1956-1971 (Box 21)
  - Powers, Robert T., 1961-1965 (Box 21)
  - Prager, William, 1967-1968, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Prakash, Anand, 1974 (Box 21)
  - Prasanna, A. R., 1971 (Box 21)
  - Pratt, Marjory Bates, 1954-1960, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1967 (Box 21)
    Bergmann, Peter G.
  - Press, William H., 1972-1976 (Box 21)
    W. H. Freeman and Co., Publishers
  - Presti, David E., 1974-1975 (Box 21)
  - Price, Don K., 1966-1968 (Box 21)
  - Primack, Joel R., 1966-1975 (Box 21)
  - Primakoff, Henry, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Princeton University, 1961-1970, n.d. (Box 21)
    Goheen, Robert Francis; U.S. Atomic Energy Commission. -- See also Series I: Goheen, Robert Francis; Putnam, Mildred A.
  - Princeton University. Department of Physics. Growth Committee, 1961-1964; 2.0 folders (Box 21)
    Bleakney, Walker (1961-62); Dicke, R[obert] H. (1961-62); Drake, R.M. (1962); Fitch, V[al] (1962); Goheen, R[obert] F. (1962); Hamilton, D.R. (1961); Hill, Julian N. (1961); Joseph Henry Club (1961); Lemonick, Aaron (1961); Ludwig, Richard M. (1962); O'Neill, Gerald (1962); Reynolds, George T. (1961-62); Sherr, Rubby (1961); Sponsler, George C. (1962); Treiman, S[amuel] B. (1961); White, M[ilton] G. (1962); Wightman, A.S. (1962)
  - Princeton University. Jadwin and Fine Halls. Dedication, 1969-1970 (Box 21)
    Bessire, Henry E. (1969); Bleakney, Walker (1969-70); Fox, F. (1969); Goheen, Robert F. (1969-70); Gordon, Ernest (1970); Putnam, Peter (1969); Smyth, H.D. (1969); Van Vranken, Robert E., Jr. (1969-70); Vivian, L.L., Jr. (1969)
  - Princeton University. Mathematical Physics Committee, 1958-1968 (Box 22)
    Bleakney, Walker (1964); [Brill], Dieter (1961); Goldberger, Marvin (1958, 1964); Heisenberg, W[erner] (1959); Malik, Fazley Bary (1959); Penrose, Roger (1965); Rasmussen, John O. (1958); Shenstone, A[llen] G. (1958)
  - Princeton University Press, 1971-1973 (Box 22)
    Bailey, Herbert S., Jr. -- See also Series I: Einstein Papers; Eiseley, Loren; Forman, Paul L.; Muller-Markus, Siegfried; Schmutzer, Ernst
  - Probst, David, 1973-1974 (Box 22)
  - Protopopescu, S., 1968 (Box 22)
  - Pryce, M. H. L., 1975 (Box 22)
  - Purcell, Edward M., 1974, n.d. (Box 22)
    -- See also Series I: Baierlein, Ralph Frederick; Dicke, Robert H.
  - Putnam, Mildred A. (Mrs. John B.), 1954-1975 (Box 22)
    Johnson, Philip C.; Oppenheimer, J. Robert; Princeton University; Putnam, Peter. -- See also Series I: Gerlach, Ulrich (1966); Putnam, Peter; Shrock, Robert; Swanson, Claude V., Jr. (1972)
  - Putnam, Peter, 1954-1975; 2.0 folders (Box 22)
    Fuller, Robert W.; Lewis, Margaret N.; Putnam, Mildred A. -- See also Series I: Eisenhart, Luther P. (1957); Fuller, Robert W.; Misner, Charles W. (1955); Putnam, Mildred. -- See also Series III: Gravitational Radiation
  - Pyenson, Lewis, 1975 (Box 22)
  - Quale, Andreas, 1968-1971, n.d. (Box 22)
  - Quesada, E. R., 1958 (Box 22)
  - Quine, Willard Van Orman, 1974-1975 (Box 22)
  - Rabi, I. I., 1967 (Box 22)
    -- See also Series I: JASON (Project 137) (1957)
  - Radicati, Gianne, 1974 (Box 22)
  - Radicati, Luca, 1975 (Box 22)
  - Radicati, Luigi A., 1975 (Box 22)
  - Radwan, Stan, 1975 (Box 22)
  - Rahm, Elizabeth, 1974-1975 (Box 22)
  - Rahn, Hermann, n.d. (Box 22)
  - Rainich, G. Y., 1957 (Box 22)
    -- See also Series I: Einstein, Albert (1925)
  - Rainwater, Leo James, 1975, n.d. (Box 22)
  - Ramsay, Norman, 1955 (Box 22)
  - Ramstad, Linda, 1965, n.d. (Box 22)
  - Randers, Gunnar, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Rapp, Carl S., 1962-1963, n.d. (Box 22)
  - Rasmussen, John O., [1954]-1969 (Box 22)
  - Rauscher, Elizabeth A., 1974-1976 (Box 22)
  - Ray, Dipankar, 1970 (Box 22)
    Roy, S. C.
  - Raychaudhuri, Amalkumar K., 1963-1964 (Box 22)
  - Rayski, Jerzy, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Recami, Erasmo, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Redfield, Andrew, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Redish, Edward Frederick, 1962-1965 (Box 23)
  - Rees, Martin J., 1971-1975 (Box 23)
    -- See also Series I: Ruffini, Remo
  - Rees, Mina, 1970 (Box 23)
  - Regge, Tullio, 1956-1974 (Box 23)
    Regge, Rosanna Caster. -- See also Series I: Eisenhart, Luther P. (1957)
  - Reich, Dan, 1955 (Box 23)
  - Reines, Frederick, 1954-1976 (Box 23)
    -- See also Series I: Burton, Ann (1951); Klauder, Louis Thornton, Jr. (1958)
  - Reischauer, Edwin Oldfather, n.d. (Box 23)
  - Rej, Anup Kumar, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Renfrew, Dwight, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Reviews of Modern Physics, 1972-1975 (Box 23)
    DeWitt, Bryce S.; Pines, David
  - Reviews of Modern Physics, Ad Hoc Committee on the Future of, 1966-1967 (Box 23)
    American Physical Society; Condon, Edward U.; Dresden, Max; Goudsmit, Sam A.; Havens, W. W., Jr.; Herring, [William] Conyers; Milford, F. J.; Townes, Charles H.; Yang, C. N.
  - Reynolds, George Thomas, 1971-1973 (Box 23)
  - Reynolds, John Hamilton, n.d. (Box 23)
  - Rhoads, Clifford E., Jr., 1969-1971 (Box 23)
  - Rice, Stuart Alan, n.d. (Box 23)
  - Rickover, Hyman, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Rideout, Louise, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Riml, Harald, 1974 (Box 23)
    Goldberger, Marvin Leonard; Wightman, Arthur
  - Rindler, Wolfgang, 1969-1971 (Box 23)
  - Ritter, James Gordon, 1964-1973 (Box 23)
  - Ritterbush, Philip C., 1975 (Box 23)
  - Robbins, Jeffrey H., 1975 (Box 23)
  - Roberts, K. V., 1954 (Box 23)
  - Robertson, H. P., 1954 (Box 23)
  - Robinson, David, 1974 (Box 23)
  - Robinson, Ivor, 1963-1971 (Box 23)
  - Robson, Donald, 1966-1971 (Box 23)
  - Rocher, E. Y., 1974 (Box 23)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1974 (Box 23)
    Allen, Jane
  - Roeder, John L., 1963 (Box 23)
  - Rogers, Eric M., 1966-1975 (Box 23)
    McClelland, G.
  - Rohrlich, Daniel, 1973-1975 (Box 23)
  - Roman, Paul, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Roos, Alice [Marie], 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - Root, Lin, 1974 (Box 23)
  - Rose, M. E., 1962-1963 (Box 23)
    Schlegel, Richard (1962)
  - Rosen, Gerald, 1970 (Box 23)
  - Rosen, Nathan, 1959, 1976 (Box 23)
    Peres, Asher. -- See also Series I: Peres, Asher
  - Rosenfeld, Leon, 1963, 1973 (Box 23)
    -- See also Series I: Michel, Louis; Rosenfeld, Yvonne (Mrs. Leon)
  - Rosenfeld, Yvonne (Mrs. Leon), 1974 (Box 23)
    Rosenfeld, Leon
  - Rosner, Jonathan, 1963-1964 (Box 23)
  - Rossler, Otto E., 1974 (Box 23)
  - Rothman, Tony, 1974 (Box 23)
  - Rowe, E. G. Peter, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
  - Ruark, Arthur E., 1959, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Rubinowicz, W., 1957 (Box 23)
  - Rucker, Rudolf B., 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - Ruderman, Sheldon, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Ruelle, David, 1974, n.d. (Box 23)
  - Ruffini, Remo, 1967-1975; 2.0 folders (Box 24)
    Bahcall, John; Jackson, Henry M.; Rees, Martin J.; Thorne, Kip S. -- See also Series I: Deruelle, Nathalie; Thorne, Kip S.
  - Rumer, Yu. B., 1969 (Box 24)
  - Runcorn, S. Keith, 1965-1974 (Box 24)
    -- See also Series I: Bussard, Robert W.; University of Newcastle Upon Tyne
  - Rusk, Dean, 1974 (Box 24)
  - Russell, Bertrand (Sir), 1967 (Box 24)
  - Ryan, Michael P., Jr., 1970-1973 (Box 24)
  - Saavedra, Igor, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Sachs, Alexander, 1968 (Box 24)
  - Sachs, Mendel, 1969-1972 (Box 24)
  - Sachs, Rainer K., 1961-1974 (Box 24)
    Allard, Bill (1974); Case, Kenneth Myron; Wightman, Arthur Strong (1974)
  - Sachs, Robert Green, n.d. (Box 24)
  - Safko, John L., 1970 (Box 24)
  - Sailor, Vance L., 1955 (Box 24)
  - Sakharov, Andrei, 1968-1976, n.d. (Box 24)
    Bers, Lipman; Halperin, Israel; Kaufmann, William J.; Ne'eman, Yuval
  - Salam, Abdus, 1969-1971 (Box 24)
  - Salisbury, Winfield W., 1973 (Box 24)
  - Salpeter, Edwin E., 1966-1967, n.d. (Box 24)
  - Salvini, G[iorgio], 1974-1975 (Box 24)
  - Samuel, Stuart Alan, 1973-1975 (Box 24)
  - Sandberg, Vernon, 1975 (Box 24)
    Kuchar, Karel V.
  - Sandoval Vallarta, Manuel, 1974 (Box 24)
  - Santorinaeos, [?], 1973 (Box 24)
  - Sarfatti, Jack, 1972-1976 (Box 24)
    Wolf, Fred A. -- See also Series I: Motz, Lloyd
  - Sargent, Robert S., 1975 (Box 24)
  - Sartori, Leo, 1958-1971 (Box 24)
  - Saslaw, William, 1965 (Box 24)
  - Saunders, Leslie, [1972] (Box 24)
    Callan, Curtis [Gove, Jr.]; Soper, Davison
  - Sawicki, Jerzy J., 1957-1967 (Box 24)
  - Scalapino, Douglas J., 1965-1972 (Box 24)
  - Schadel, Harry Marion III, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Scharff-Goldhaber, Gertrude, n.d. (Box 24)
  - Schawlow, Arthur L., n.d. (Box 24)
  - Schiffer, John Paul, n.d. (Box 24)
  - Schiffer, Menahem Max, n.d. (Box 24)
  - Schild, Alfred, 1966-1975 (Box 24)
  - Schiller, Ralph, 1969 (Box 24)
  - Schlesinger, James R., 1974 (Box 24)
  - Schlobohm, Dean Alfred, 1969 (Box 24)
  - Schmenner, Roger William, 1968 (Box 24)
  - Schmitt, [?], [1975] (Box 24)
  - Schmutzer, Ernst, 1971 (Box 24)
  - Schnatterly, Stephen E., 1969, n.d. (Box 24)
  - Schouten, J. A., 1956 (Box 24)
  - Schrank, Glenn, 1955, 1969-1970 (Box 24)
  - Schucking, Engelbert L., 1961-1973 (Box 25)
  - Schulman, L[awrence] S., 1965, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Schumacher, D[onald] L., 1973 (Box 25)
  - Schutz, Bernard F., Jr., 1972-1975 (Box 25)
  - Schutz, Stephen A., 1967-1969, n.d. (Box 25)
  - Schvartsman, V. F., 1974 (Box 25)
  - Schwartz, Melvin, n.d. (Box 25)
  - Schwartz, Robert, 1968 (Box 25)
  - Schwarz, John, 1968 (Box 25)
    Weinberg, Steven
  - Schwarzschild, Martin, 1976 (Box 25)
    -- See also Series I: Wende, Charles
  - Schwejda, [?], 1973 (Box 25)
  - Schwenk, Robert, 1973 (Box 25)
  - Schwinger, Julian, 1968-1969, n.d. (Box 25)
  - Sciama, Dennis W., 1959-1976 (Box 25)
    Clarendon Press (1974). -- See also Series I: Gilman, Robert C.
  - Science, 1973 (Box 25)
    -- See also Series I: Wigner, Eugene P.
  - Science Year, 1971-1972 (Box 25)
    Tilleux, Wade
  - Scientific American, 1967 (Box 25)
    Piel, Gerard
  - Scott, Dana S., 1973-1976 (Box 25)
    Kuchar, Karel V.; Misner, Charles W.; Penrose, Roger
  - Scoville, Herbert, Jr., 1963 (Box 25)
  - Scranton, William Warren, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1974 (Box 25)
    Heuer, Kenneth
  - Seaborg, Glenn T., 1967-1971 (Box 25)
  - Seagondollar, [L.W.], 1972 (Box 25)
  - Sedov, L[eonid] I., 1976 (Box 25)
  - Segal, Irving, 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Segre, Beniamino, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Segre, Emilio, 1973 (Box 25)
  - Seilenthal, Mats, 1968 (Box 25)
  - Seitman, David, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Seitz, Frederick, 1964-1971 (Box 25)
    -- See also Series I: Hutchisson, Elmer
  - Sejnowski, Terrence J., 1969-1976 (Box 25)
    Trautman, Andrzej
  - Seldner, [?], 1973 (Box 25)
  - Serber, Robert, 1968-1969, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Setti, Gian-Carlo, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Seyboldt, Leonora W., 1973-1975 (Box 25)
  - Sexl, Roman U., 1973-1976 (Box 25)
  - Shamos, Michael Ian, 1967-1975 (Box 25)
  - Shapiro, Maurice M., 1974 (Box 25)
  - Sharp, David H., 1960-1975 (Box 25)
    -- See also Series I: Bardeen, James M.
  - Shaw, Charles H., 1967 (Box 25)
  - Sheldon, John W., 1968-1974 (Box 25)
  - Shelupsky, David Irwin, 1959-1962 (Box 25)
  - Shenstone, Allen G., 1956, n.d. (Box 25)
  - Shepley, Lawrence C., 1961-1974 (Box OS1, Box 25)
    Princeton University Press. -- See also Oversized
  - Sheppard, Eli Taylor, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Sherr, Rubby, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Sherwin, Charles W., 1957-1960 (Box 25)
  - Shneiderov, Anatol J., 1973-1974 (Box 25)
  - Shockley, William, 1972-[1974] (Box 25)
  - Shrock, Robert, 1975 (Box 25)
    Putnam, [Mildred A.] (Mrs. John)
  - Shukla, [?], 1965 (Box 25)
  - Shull, [?], 1973 (Box 25)
  - Siebers, Bernard H., Jr., 1973 (Box 25)
  - Silber, John R., 1973 (Box 25)
  - Silverman, Shirleigh, 1974-1975 (Box 25)
  - Silverstein, Martin Louis, 1961-1963 (Box 25)
  - Simon, Barry, 1973-1976 (Box 25)
  - Simpson, John F., 1963 (Box 25)
  - Singer, S. Fred, 1963-1970, n.d. (Box 25)
    Strauss, Lewis L.
  - Sklar, Alfred, 1969, n.d. (Box 25)
    Ferrer, Olga
  - Slaby, Steve M., 1965 (Box 25)
  - Slack, Lewis, 1968 (Box 25)
  - Slade, Afton, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Slichter, Charles Pence, n.d. (Box 25)
  - Smale, Stephen, 1966, n.d. (Box 25)
  - Smarr, Larry Lee, 1969-1976 (Box 25)
  - Smith, Cyril, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Smith, James P., 1974 (Box 25)
  - Smith, William V., 1973 (Box 25)
  - Smithey, William J. H., 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Smithsonian Institution Press, 1974-1976 (Box 25)
    American Scientist; Horn, Joan; Wilder, Catharine
  - Smoluchowski, Roman, 1967-1970, n.d. (Box 25)
    Pines, David
  - Smyth, Henry DeWolf, 1974 (Box 25)
    -- See also Series I: Strauss, Lewis L.
  - Snow, Gregory R., 1974 (Box 25)
  - Society of Physics Students, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr I., 1975, n.d. (Box 25)
  - Sommers, Paul Daniel, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Sondheim, Alan, 1972-[1973] (Box 25)
  - Soneira, Raymond M., 1973 (Box 25)
  - Sources for History of Quantum Physics, 1960-1976; 17.0 folders (Box 26-28)